>> Jem Young: 好的，这是它。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right, this is it.
我们现在就在家里
We're in the home stretch now.
我们建立了我们的服务器，我们刚刚安装了节点。
We've built our server,
we just installed Node.
所以现在我们想把它弄上去
So now we wanna get Node up and running.
我们希望允许它接受请求并适当地处理它们。
We wanna allow it to accept requests and
handle them appropriately.
然后我们想把它放在背景里然后我们想用某种
And then we wanna keep it running in the
background, then we wanna use some sort of
版本控制以确保我们在出错时可以随时回滚。
version control to make sure that we can
rollback at anytime if we make mistakes.
简单来说，应用体系结构。
Let's talk about, briefly,
application architecture.
如果你问我一个高级工程师和
If you ask me what the difference
is between a senior engineer and
一个初级工程师我说它是关于建筑的
a junior engineer,
I'd say it's about architecture.
这不是关于代码，它是关于建筑的。
It's not about code,
it's about the architecture.
从长远来说，它是将会得到你的架构和应用。
Cuz in the long run, it's the architecture
and application that will get you.
它是如何排列文件，如何排列代码的方式。
It's how you arrange your files,
how you arrange your code.
我们考虑的是长期的可维护性
That sort of thing is we're thinking about
long-term maintainability versus just,
我是个黑客每天都能解决虫子
I'm a hacker who solves bugs every day.
这更像是一个初级工程师，高级工程师认为是长期的。
That's more like a junior engineer,
senior engineers think long-term.
所以当我们建立一个应用程序架构时，记住它会为
So when we set up an application
architecture, remember, it will live for
可能是很久很久了
a long time, maybe years.
所以你想让它以一种对你有意义的方式
So you want to make sure it's set up
in a way that makes sense to you and
每个人都能同意
everybody can agree on.
因为迁移文件不好玩， [ LAUGH] 是痛苦的。
Because migrating files is not fun,
[LAUGH] it is painful.
其实我刚才只是说了很久以前关于密码的事
Actually, I just gave a talk not
too long ago about using code mods,
我必须重写一堆 JavaScript 代码
cuz I had to rewrite a bunch
of JavaScript code, and
使用代码模型是有效的方法
using code mods is an efficient
way of doing that.
这可能有个课
There's probably a class on that.
如果代码上没有课值就值了
If there's not a class on code mods,
it's worth taking.
它更先进，但上面有一类，我也会链接到这个。
It's more advanced, but there's a class
on that and I'll link to that as well.
但在基本应用架构方面，如果你说的是
But in terms of basic application
architecture, if you're talking about
你最简单的最基本的建筑，这可能是一个好的设置。
your most simplest, basic architecture,
this is probably a good setup.
你也许不同意这很好
You may disagree, and that's fine.
这是我通常使用的
This is the one I usually use.
所以我用了 ui ，然后我用 css， js， html。
So I use ui, and then I use css, js, html.
然后在 ui 外，我用帮手， utils。
Then outside of ui, I use helpers, utils.
也许是为了认证
Maybe something for authentication.
如果我想和数据库谈谈的话，我把所有这些都放在 UI之外。
If I ever want to talk to database,
I put all that outside UI.
但我试图在他们所代表的文件夹中约束它。
But I try to constrain it within
the folders that they represent.
这不像是大事但是长远来说如果你要做一个全新的品牌
This doesn't seem like a big deal, but in
the long run, if you're making a brand new
应用程序和您的业务，您的架构就会迎头赶上。
application and you turn into a business,
your architecture will catch up to you.
就像 Facebook 的早期依赖 PHP ，结果是
Much like Facebook depended early
days on PHP, and it turns out,
人们不喜欢 PHP
people don't like PHP.
但现在他们创造了一个完整的编译器
But now they have they
created an entire compiler so
人们还可以写 PHP 来编译其他的东西，
people can still write PHP to
compile to something else,
因为他们很早就做出了决定
because of these early decisions
that they made early on.
我在纽约的一个创业公司工作，决定使用 Google 关闭。
I worked at a startup in New York,
which decided to use Google Closure.
不是 J， S，
So not the J, the S,
谷歌内部开发的那种晦涩的语言
the really kind of obscure language
that Google developed internally.
因为我和这个人在谷歌工作，我们看到了谷歌的关闭。
And because this person and I worked at
Google, we saw to use Google Closure.
后来我们付了钱因为没人使用闭包
And we paid for that later
because no one uses Closure, and
我得去看那些不存在的东西
[LAUGH] I had to look stuff
up that didn't exist.
所以我想说的是全部堆的一部分你得做出决定
So all I'm saying is part of full
stack is you have to make the decision
关于你的申请
about your application.
你要用的那堆
The stack that you're gonna use.
你要用的密码
The code you're gonna use.
想想，别人能用吗 ?
And think about, can other people use it?
或者你只是在用它，因为它很酷吗 ?
Or are you just using
it because it's cool?
你是在用鲁斯特什么的，不是很多人知道的吗 ?
Are you just using Rust or something,
that not many people know?
还是哈斯凯尔
Or Haskell?
还是利斯普 [ LAUGH] 或某种类型的列表语言。
Or Lisp?
[LAUGH] Or some sort of list language.
这对你很酷，但如果你要登上 20 个人，他们知道 Lisp吗 ?
Which is cool to you, but if you're gonna
on-board 20 people, do they know Lisp?
他们是否了解您的应用程序体系结构?
Do they understand your
application architecture?
如果你说测试在这里代码就在这里
If you say, the tests are over here and
the code is over here, and
你想想别人怎么用你的代码
it all makes sense to you, think
about how other people use your code.
抱歉我知道我要去建筑学
Sorry, I know I'm going on
about architecture, but
这些东西是很重要的我们不太想太多
this stuff is really important,
it's something we don't think about a lot.
但以你想要的方式来设置代码。
But set your code up in
the way that you want.
当你想到这种结构的时候，你会发现它会变得更容易。
And you'll see it's a lot easier when you
think in terms of this sort of structure.